Part of the fun of Pokemon is that it is a collectible card game.
A lot of you might look at the amount of cards that you could amass over quite a bit of time and you think what the heck am I going to do with all these cards?
Well the fun part is building different kinds of decks.
You don't have to play with the same deck.
You can always build yourself different decks, keep one build another one, build another one.
That's why I've got all these cards.
Sometimes I feel like playing fire, sometimes I feel like playing water.
A lot of people are used to when you are playing card games and you have got the one deck of cards and you just play with that deck over and over again it never changes.
With Pokemon you build your own deck, use different creatures, different energies and you play with that deck or a different deck you build and that is sort of the difference is that you don't use the same deck of cards and that is one of the reasons it makes it a collectible card game because you collect all these cards to make all these different decks.
I would love for my assistant here to show you many of his different decks that he has built over time.
I have a fighting deck, an electric deck, my mummy's deck which is full of Cue Pokemon, my fire deck, my Earth deck and finally my water deck.
Now do you play with all these decks at different times?
Oh yea, I play with all of them.
Which one is your favorite?
I kind of like my killer deck.
Your killer deck.
What's in your killer deck?
A bunch of ex's.
Oh.